CURRICULUM VITAE

Andrés Julián León

Mobile: +354 831 7671

Email: ion.vector@gmail.com

Date of birth: april 19, 1980

Country of origin: Colombia

Current country of residence: Iceland

PROFILE

Web Developer and Graphic Designer. Focused on front-end web development, data visualization and user experience and interfaces (UX/UI). Experience in infographics, branding, digital visual concepts and illustration.

Creative and with own discernment, with a defined sense of professional ethics, teamwork, and commitment. Highly interested in research, learning and development of new skills.

SKILLS

HTML5: * * * *

CSS: * * * * *

JavaScript: * * *

JQuery: * * *

WebGL: * * *

Python: *

PHP: *

Java: *
C++: *

WordPress: * * * *

Brackets: * * * *

Diackets:

Adobe XD * * * * * Illustrator: * * * *

Photoshop: * * * *

EDUCATION

1998 ICFES

High School degree. Bogotá, Colombia.

2007 UNITEC

Graphic Production and Design.Bachelor of Technology degree.

Bogotá, Colombia.

2016 ICELAND ACADEMY OF THE ARTS

MA in Design.
Master's degree.
Reykjavik, Iceland.

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Spanish: Native
English: Fluent
Swedish: Beginner

Icelandic: Beginner

COMPLEMENTARY EDUCATION

2005 **CAFAM**

Web Design

Complementary course. Bogotá, Colombia.

2013 COURSERA

Introduction to Mathematical Thinking

MOOC course.

Introduction to Psychology

MOOC course.

Video Games and Learning

MOOC course.

2014 Social Psychology

MOOC course.

Gamification

MOOC course.

Programming for Everybody(Python)

MOOC course.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2017 Karousel.

Web Designer / Developer

Website designer and developer.

Contractor work.

2015 – 2017 Windsor Language System LLC, Bogotá.

Web Application Developer

Website and web app developer.

Contractor work.

2015 – 2016 Visual Gloow, Bogotá.

Web developer

Website development.

Full time work.

2009 – 2016 **JC Detector Radiation, Bogotá.**

Webmaster

Website and hosting administration, corporate email

administration, infographics. Part time/contractor work.

2007 – present ICC Limitada, Bogotá.

Webmaster

Website and hosting administration, graphic design and 3D concept artist.

Part time/contractor work.

PERSONAL REFERENCES

Marco Aurelio Arenas Windsor Language System LLC.

Ph.D. President

Email: sandsmar@aol.com

Camilo Vallejo Deutsche Bank

Finance Specialist and Manager

Email: camilo.vallejo@db.com

Javier Zalaba O. ICC Limitada

Deputy General Manager

Email: javierzabalao@icclimitada.com